<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Nailak Blog – Beauty and Wellness Tips</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nailak Blog – Beauty and Wellness Tips</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 04:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.nailak.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#SHIRLEYSFAVESANDFINDS #36 — Daily routine for strong healthy nails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/%23shirleysfavesandfinds-%2336-daily-routine-for-strong-healthy-nails/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 04:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/%23shirleysfavesandfinds-%2336-daily-routine-for-strong-healthy-nails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="daily-routine-for-strong-healthy-nails"&gt;Daily Routine for Strong, Healthy Nails&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — not to critique, but to check in. The week had been a swirl of calendar blocks, click-clacking keys, a quick sink full of dishes, a last-minute workout class. In the middle of it all, her nails told a story. A soft sheen. A small snag. A faint white mark at the edge where she’d opened a package without thinking. Nothing dramatic, just the everyday proof that life moves fast.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Stéphane Rolland to showcase at Barcelona Bridal Night as international guest label — Vegan nail oil for cuticles</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/st%C3%A9phane-rolland-to-showcase-at-barcelona-bridal-night-as-international-guest-label-vegan-nail-oil-for-cuticles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 03:56:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/st%C3%A9phane-rolland-to-showcase-at-barcelona-bridal-night-as-international-guest-label-vegan-nail-oil-for-cuticles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="bridal-nails-vegan-cuticle-oil-meets-barcelona-couture"&gt;Bridal Nails: Vegan Cuticle Oil Meets Barcelona Couture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The mug was warm. The room still smelled faintly of last night’s peonies. Outside, the sky held that pale, anticipatory light that feels like a promise. She turned her hand and saw the tiniest crescent of dryness along her cuticle — the spot that always catches on sweaters, the one she swears isn’t a big deal until it is. Her calendar nudged an alert. Bridal season was cresting. Even if she wasn’t the one walking down the aisle, the energy was everywhere: fittings, fabric swatches, joy in motion. And with it came the desire for polish that didn’t just look perfect, but felt like her — calm, cared for, luminous.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Best Lip Balm to Protect Against Wind and Cold — Essential oils for cuticle health</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/the-best-lip-balm-to-protect-against-wind-and-cold-essential-oils-for-cuticle-health/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/the-best-lip-balm-to-protect-against-wind-and-cold-essential-oils-for-cuticle-health/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="best-lip-balm-for-wind-and-cold--cuticle-oils"&gt;Best Lip Balm for Wind and Cold + Cuticle Oils&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. Outside, winter was rehearsing its drama. Wind threaded through city streets, tugging at hemlines and tempering cheeks to pink. Inside, the office hummed with deadlines, dry heat, and the tap-tap of keyboards. It was the season of steaming mugs and wool scarves. It was also the season of chapped lips and frayed cuticles.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Step Into Confidence: Find Your Perfect Pair at ROSATINA — How to fix nail peeling and splitting</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/step-into-confidence-find-your-perfect-pair-at-rosatina-how-to-fix-nail-peeling-and-splitting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/step-into-confidence-find-your-perfect-pair-at-rosatina-how-to-fix-nail-peeling-and-splitting/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="fix-nail-peeling-step-into-confidence-with-rosatina"&gt;Fix Nail Peeling: Step Into Confidence With ROSATINA&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The travel mug warmed her palms. Steam curled up like a ribbon, catching the early light. Her nails, though, told a different story: tiny white flakes at the tips, a split at the corner of her index finger, and a snag threatening to catch on a sweater. She sighed. It was a familiar frustration — one that seemed to pop up right when everything else was in motion.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Jo Malone Wood Sage and Sea Salt Cologne Review — Hangnail prevention tips</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/jo-malone-wood-sage-and-sea-salt-cologne-review-hangnail-prevention-tips/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/22/jo-malone-wood-sage-and-sea-salt-cologne-review-hangnail-prevention-tips/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="wood-sage--sea-salt-scent-review--nail-care"&gt;Wood Sage &amp;amp; Sea Salt: Scent Review + Nail Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. A spritz of Jo Malone Wood Sage &amp;amp; Sea Salt drifted up, bright and mineral, like the first breath on a windswept beach. The mist caught the light, then the moment caught her: a tiny twinge along the side of her index finger. Another hangnail waiting to snag a sweater or a mood. It’s funny how beauty works like that. One sense elevates; another asks for attention.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>5 FRUMPY OUTFITS I USED TO WEAR! 😂 Part 4 — Natural vs synthetic nail care products</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/5-frumpy-outfits-i-used-to-wear-part-4-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-products/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/5-frumpy-outfits-i-used-to-wear-part-4-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-products/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-what-works"&gt;Natural vs Synthetic Nail Care: What Works&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a moment between buttoning a jacket and stepping out the door when you catch your reflection and think, Is this me? Some days, a well-meaning oversized sweater and comfy flats become a little too relaxed. The outfit skews frumpy instead of cozy-chic. And yet… your nails can whisper a different story. A gentle nude, a sculpted oval, a gloss that looks like raindrops over porcelain — suddenly the whole look sharpens.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Low Maintenance Medium Length Haicuts To Revamp Your Style This Summer — Non toxic nail polish alternatives</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/low-maintenance-medium-length-haicuts-to-revamp-your-style-this-summer-non-toxic-nail-polish-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/low-maintenance-medium-length-haicuts-to-revamp-your-style-this-summer-non-toxic-nail-polish-alternatives/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="low-maintenance-medium-cuts--non-toxic-nail-polish"&gt;Low-Maintenance Medium Cuts &amp;amp; Non-Toxic Nail Polish&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She tucked a loose strand behind her ear, the kind of sunlit morning where the city moved slower and the iced latte slid condensation onto her fingers. A light breeze lifted her shoulder-grazing hair—soft, shiny, and already half-dry from the walk. No blowout. No forty-minute routine. Just a quick scrunch with leave-in cream before she ran out the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the café table, she noticed her nails—soft pink with a silky, almost glassy gloss. Not a chemical cloud in sight, just a clean formula that let her nails breathe. The manicure looked simple and fresh, the sort of quiet detail that boosts your mood all day. She smiled, because some days beauty should feel effortless. Like the haircut you wake up with and it still looks good. Like polish that doesn’t make your eyes sting or chip the moment you step into a grocery line.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Perricone MD Triple Retinol Renewal Review — How to moisturize nails and cuticles</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/perricone-md-triple-retinol-renewal-review-how-to-moisturize-nails-and-cuticles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:36:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/perricone-md-triple-retinol-renewal-review-how-to-moisturize-nails-and-cuticles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="perricone-md-triple-retinol-review--cuticle-care"&gt;Perricone MD Triple Retinol Review &amp;amp; Cuticle Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. Maybe you know that moment. The light hits just right, and you notice the stories your hands are telling — the keyboard clicks, the dishwater hours, the late-night scrolling. The back of your hand looks a bit dull, the cuticles a touch ragged. You flex your fingers and think, I should treat these better. It’s not vanity. It’s tenderness.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>REVLON ColorStay Flex Wear Full Cover Concealer — Nail fungus treatment</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/revlon-colorstay-flex-wear-full-cover-concealer-nail-fungus-treatment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/21/revlon-colorstay-flex-wear-full-cover-concealer-nail-fungus-treatment/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="nail-fungus-care--revlon-flex-wear-concealer"&gt;Nail Fungus Care + Revlon Flex Wear Concealer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the warm mug, the quick comfort, the little pause before the day took over. The latte art had already softened at the edges, but her mind was somewhere else. On her nails. On that one stubborn toenail that showed through her sandal last weekend. On the way she curled her fingers around her cup to keep a tiny patch of discoloration out of view. It wasn’t vanity. It was the very human desire to feel put-together, to feel good in your own skin — and yes, your own nails.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Why 5G Is a Game Changer for Everyday Users — Daily routine for strong healthy nails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/why-5g-is-a-game-changer-for-everyday-users-daily-routine-for-strong-healthy-nails/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/why-5g-is-a-game-changer-for-everyday-users-daily-routine-for-strong-healthy-nails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="5g-life-faster-days--a-strong-healthy-nail-routine"&gt;5G Life: Faster Days &amp;amp; A Strong, Healthy Nail Routine&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. Steam curled from her mug, her phone buzzed with meeting updates, and in those few uninterrupted minutes, a tiny routine unfolded. A quick scroll to a saved tutorial, a minute-long massage with cuticle oil, a short timer to let the product sink in. No drama, no rush, just a touch of calm before the next video call.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Liquid Blush vs Powder Blush: Which Formula Delivers the Best Results for Your Skin? — Vegan nail oil for cuticles</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/liquid-blush-vs-powder-blush-which-formula-delivers-the-best-results-for-your-skin-vegan-nail-oil-for-cuticles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:05:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/liquid-blush-vs-powder-blush-which-formula-delivers-the-best-results-for-your-skin-vegan-nail-oil-for-cuticles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="liquid-or-powder-blush-plus-vegan-cuticle-care"&gt;Liquid or Powder Blush? Plus Vegan Cuticle Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The steam curled around her cup, blending with the delicate scent of citrus from last night’s cuticle oil. On her cheeks, the flush was just right: not too glowy, not too matte. She’d finally nailed it — the balance between liquid blush and powder blush — and found a rhythm that made busy mornings feel less like a rush and more like a ritual.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Makeup and Beauty Blog Monday Poll, Vol. 897 — Essential oils for cuticle health</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-and-beauty-blog-monday-poll-vol.-897-essential-oils-for-cuticle-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:50:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-and-beauty-blog-monday-poll-vol.-897-essential-oils-for-cuticle-health/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="essential-oils-for-cuticle-health-a-modern-guide"&gt;Essential Oils for Cuticle Health: A Modern Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. Maybe you’ve had a moment like that too. A pause. Steam rising from your mug. The weight of your day arranging itself around a single choice: be gentle with yourself, or keep rushing. It’s often our hands that tell the truth first. They show our pace. They show our habits. And when the skin around our nails turns tight, rough, or ragged, that little flare of discomfort can echo through everything we do.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How to Do Spooky (But Cute!) Halloween Nails at Home — How to fix nail peeling and splitting</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/how-to-do-spooky-but-cute-halloween-nails-at-home-how-to-fix-nail-peeling-and-splitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/how-to-do-spooky-but-cute-halloween-nails-at-home-how-to-fix-nail-peeling-and-splitting/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="spooky-cute-halloween-nails-at-home-no-damage"&gt;Spooky-Cute Halloween Nails at Home (No Damage)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break—the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The brisk October air pressed against the window. A sweater cuff grazed knuckles that had known too many rushed dishwashing sessions and not enough cuticle oil. There were tiny splits at the free edge, a nick from an old metal file, and the faint ghost of last week’s polish.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The 10 Most Common Addictions: A Guide To Breaking Free — Hangnail prevention tips</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/the-10-most-common-addictions-a-guide-to-breaking-free-hangnail-prevention-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/the-10-most-common-addictions-a-guide-to-breaking-free-hangnail-prevention-tips/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hangnail-prevention-break-the-picking-habit"&gt;Hangnail Prevention: Break the Picking Habit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She noticed it during her quick coffee stop—the tiniest flap of skin by her thumbnail, catching softly on the paper cup. It was nothing dramatic, just a whisper of roughness against a smooth morning. On the walk back, the urge bloomed. She told herself she would leave it alone, but the familiar loop began anyway—rub, tug, relief, sting. The skin reddened. Hand sanitizer made it burn. Later, typing hurt. She tucked the finger into a sleeve like a secret.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>La Mer vs Carrot &amp; Stick — Natural vs synthetic nail care products</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/la-mer-vs-carrot-stick-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/la-mer-vs-carrot-stick-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-products/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="la-mer-vs-carrot--stick-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care"&gt;La Mer vs Carrot &amp;amp; Stick: Natural vs Synthetic Nail Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. A few hours earlier, she’d patted in a velvety cream between emails, massaged a drop of oil into her cuticles, and slipped on dish gloves before tackling the sink. Nothing glamorous. Just calm, consistent care. Now, the cuticles looked neat, the nail beds hydrated, and even the faint ridges felt softer under her thumb. It wasn’t about a perfect manicure; it was about feeling composed in the small ways that carry you through a day.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Exercises That Help Combat Muscle Loss on GLP-1s — Non toxic nail polish alternatives</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/exercises-that-help-combat-muscle-loss-on-glp-1s-non-toxic-nail-polish-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/exercises-that-help-combat-muscle-loss-on-glp-1s-non-toxic-nail-polish-alternatives/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="exercises-for-glp-1-muscle-loss--non-toxic-nail-polish"&gt;Exercises for GLP-1 Muscle Loss + Non-Toxic Nail Polish&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She paused at the kitchen counter, steam curling from her mug, and noticed her hands. A soft, healthy sheen on her nails. A strength she hadn’t seen in a while returning to her forearms. It wasn’t dramatic. It wasn’t loud. But it felt like her body whispering, I’m rebuilding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, clothes had started to fit differently. The number on the scale shifted, and with it came a wave of mixed emotions. She’d started a GLP-1 medication after a long talk with her doctor, hoping to steady habits that always felt just out of reach. Appetite eased. Meals simplified. Yet, there was a new question: was she losing more than she intended?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Avora Immersive Experience — How to moisturize nails and cuticles</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/avora-immersive-experience-how-to-moisturize-nails-and-cuticles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/avora-immersive-experience-how-to-moisturize-nails-and-cuticles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="avora-london-guide--how-to-moisturize-nails--cuticles"&gt;Avora London Guide + How to Moisturize Nails &amp;amp; Cuticles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The doors swing open and the room glows green, like a rainforest after rain. A soft mist curls through the light. The bartender—part scientist, part storyteller—slides a beaker across the bar and it hums with neon. A flower-shaped garnish opens under the rim. You sip and the flavor shifts: bright citrus, then cool pine, a whisper of floral that you can’t quite name. A hush ripples through the crowd as a curtain lifts and reveals a corridor of glowing vines. You step into the next chamber and the floor responds to your footsteps, a galaxy blooming with every move.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>MAKEUP PALETTES That Do It All — Nail strengthening treatments</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-palettes-that-do-it-all-nail-strengthening-treatments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-palettes-that-do-it-all-nail-strengthening-treatments/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="makeup-palettes-that-do-it-all--nail-strengtheners"&gt;Makeup Palettes That Do It All + Nail Strengtheners&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lights in the airport restroom hummed like a nervous bee. I had eight minutes before boarding and the kind of face that looked like it had slept under an armrest — because it had. A half-empty coffee rattled in the trash. Somewhere beyond security, a child giggled at the way the automatic sinks came to life. I unzipped a small pouch, the only one I’d brought for “getting ready,” and laid its contents on the cool counter.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>What Are Exosomes, The Lastest Skincare Ingredient Exciting Dermatologists? — What causes brittle nails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/what-are-exosomes-the-lastest-skincare-ingredient-exciting-dermatologists-what-causes-brittle-nails/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/what-are-exosomes-the-lastest-skincare-ingredient-exciting-dermatologists-what-causes-brittle-nails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="exosomes-in-skincare-and-brittle-nails-explained"&gt;Exosomes in Skincare and Brittle Nails Explained&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plane’s air vents hissed like a desert wind. By hour six, the skin on my hands felt papery, and the ridges on my thumbnails caught on the lining of my jacket. In the hotel bathroom, the mirror wobbled with a hum as the extractor fan worked. Harsh light exposed what travel always tries to hide: dullness around the eyes, a chalky veil on cheeks, and that unmistakable snag when a brittle nail meets a zipper.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>12 Hidden Rosacea Triggers You Need to Know, According to Dermatologists — DIY nail oil blend</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-you-need-to-know-according-to-dermatologists-diy-nail-oil-blend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-you-need-to-know-according-to-dermatologists-diy-nail-oil-blend/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-dermatologists-warn-about"&gt;12 Hidden Rosacea Triggers Dermatologists Warn About&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first time it happened, it felt like a match drawn across my cheekbones. Late afternoon sun bathed the café in Porto, the table crowded with friends and small plates—salty cheeses, olives slick with oil, a smear of piri-piri heat. Someone topped off my glass. The moment the wine hit, warmth bloomed across my face. Eyes prickled. Skin tightened. I reached for a napkin and realized my fingertips smelled faintly of citrus from the cuticle oil I’d rolled on an hour earlier.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>This TikTok Viral Bodycare Brand Lives Up to the Hype — How to use cuticle oil properly</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-how-to-use-cuticle-oil-properly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 23:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-how-to-use-cuticle-oil-properly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="how-to-use-cuticle-oil-the-right-way-anywhere"&gt;How to Use Cuticle Oil the Right Way, Anywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a certain sound the airport makes when a storm stalls departures. Coffee machines tempo into a low hiss. A thousand rolling suitcases drum the tiles. A PA crackles, apologizes, then goes silent. You rub your hands together because the terminal AC runs too cold, because winter air steals moisture, because the sanitizer pump by the gate is impossible to pass without a press. Your fingers feel tight and a little sore. A rough edge snags your sweater. You wince.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kylie Jenner Reheated The 'King Kylie' Aesthetic With Her 10-Year Anniversary Collection — Best cuticle oil brands</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/kylie-jenner-reheated-the-king-kylie-aesthetic-with-her-10-year-anniversary-collection-best-cuticle-oil-brands/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/kylie-jenner-reheated-the-king-kylie-aesthetic-with-her-10-year-anniversary-collection-best-cuticle-oil-brands/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="best-cuticle-oils-for-reviving-your-nails"&gt;Best Cuticle Oils for Reviving Your Nails&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the bustling world of beauty, trends come and go with the swiftness of a New York minute. It&amp;rsquo;s 2016 again, and the nostalgia of the &amp;ldquo;King Kylie&amp;rdquo; era has swept us back into the vibrant world of bold lip kits and shimmering highlighters. But as any beauty enthusiast knows, the foundation of any great look isn&amp;rsquo;t just the makeup—it&amp;rsquo;s the care that goes into the canvas itself. This time, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about something that often gets overlooked in the beauty routine: your nails.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ICYMI: Maria Grazia Chiuri Returns to Fendi, Boy Smells Opens First Flagship Pop-Up &amp; What Brands Get Out of Beauty New York — How to grow nails faster naturally</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/icymi-maria-grazia-chiuri-returns-to-fendi-boy-smells-opens-first-flagship-pop-up-what-brands-get-out-of-beauty-new-york-how-to-grow-nails-faster-naturally/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/icymi-maria-grazia-chiuri-returns-to-fendi-boy-smells-opens-first-flagship-pop-up-what-brands-get-out-of-beauty-new-york-how-to-grow-nails-faster-naturally/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="grow-nails-faster-naturally-expert-tips"&gt;Grow Nails Faster Naturally: Expert Tips&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picture this: You’re scrolling through your favorite fashion blog, and you stumble upon an article about the latest trends in nail art. The vibrant colors and intricate designs are captivating, and you can almost feel the urge to book your next manicure appointment. But there’s a hitch — your nails seem to grow at a snail’s pace. You’ve tried everything from nail strengtheners to biotin supplements, yet nothing seems to make a real difference. You sigh, feeling the frustration that many share when it comes to achieving those perfectly long and healthy nails that are always Instagram-ready.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Glossy Pop Newsletter: Lancôme is making moves to become every bride’s go-to glam — Nail growth tips at home</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/glossy-pop-newsletter-lanc%C3%B4me-is-making-moves-to-become-every-brides-go-to-glam-nail-growth-tips-at-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/glossy-pop-newsletter-lanc%C3%B4me-is-making-moves-to-become-every-brides-go-to-glam-nail-growth-tips-at-home/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="lancômes-bridal-glamour--nail-growth-tips"&gt;Lancôme&amp;rsquo;s Bridal Glamour &amp;amp; Nail Growth Tips&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine walking down the aisle, the soft hum of music enveloping you, and every eye in the room is on you. Your gown flows like a gentle stream, and your makeup — impeccable, timeless, and effortlessly radiant. For many brides, this dream moment is incomplete without the perfect makeup brand. Lancôme is stepping up to be that brand. It&amp;rsquo;s not just about the makeup; it&amp;rsquo;s about embodying elegance and sophistication on one of the most memorable days of your life.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ulta Beauty’s Marketplace Launch Sparks Customer Backlash — Nail oil vs cuticle cream</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/ulta-beautys-marketplace-launch-sparks-customer-backlash-nail-oil-vs-cuticle-cream/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/ulta-beautys-marketplace-launch-sparks-customer-backlash-nail-oil-vs-cuticle-cream/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ulta-beautys-new-marketplace-what-you-need-to-know"&gt;Ulta Beauty&amp;rsquo;s New Marketplace: What You Need to Know&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine walking into a store, your senses enveloped by the aroma of countless beauty products, each promising to transform your routine. You’re not just shopping; you&amp;rsquo;re embarking on a self-care journey. Ulta Beauty has long been a destination for beauty enthusiasts seeking everything from cult-favorite mascaras to the latest skincare innovations. In its latest move, Ulta unveiled the UB Marketplace, a digital expansion designed to offer even more variety. However, this launch hasn&amp;rsquo;t been without its hiccups.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Best Celebrity Bobs to Wear in Any Season — How to prevent hangnails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/the-best-celebrity-bobs-to-wear-in-any-season-how-to-prevent-hangnails/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/the-best-celebrity-bobs-to-wear-in-any-season-how-to-prevent-hangnails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="celebrity-bobs--hangnail-solutions"&gt;Celebrity Bobs &amp;amp; Hangnail Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the likes of Taylor Swift and Zendaya strutted onto the red carpet with their chic bob hairstyles, fans around the globe were mesmerized. The bob, with its timeless elegance and effortless charm, has taken over Hollywood. It’s not just a hairstyle—it&amp;rsquo;s a statement. But beneath the glamorous exterior lies a common beauty woe that even celebrities can’t escape: hangnails. These tiny, pesky skin tears are more than just a minor annoyance; they can be painful and even lead to infections. Imagine this: you’re about to shake hands with someone important, and there it is—a snag. It’s a moment many have experienced, yet few talk about openly.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>We're Moving! — non-toxic nail care</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/were-moving-non-toxic-nail-care/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/were-moving-non-toxic-nail-care/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="non-toxic-nail-care-the-future-of-beauty"&gt;Non-Toxic Nail Care: The Future of Beauty&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When UberChic Beauty announced its warehouse move, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a change of address. For many loyal customers, it marked the end of an era—eight years of vibrant nail art and innovative non-toxic products. The move was a testament to the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth and evolution, a reflection of how far the industry has come. “Thank you for your amazing support and for the BEST eight years we could have ever asked for,” read the heartfelt note from the founder. As fans rushed to place orders before the temporary shipping pause, the excitement was palpable. The new year promised fresh beginnings and new developments, including a special mini plate called &amp;ldquo;Happy Birthday&amp;rdquo; to celebrate the milestone.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>This TikTok Viral Bodycare Brand Lives Up to the Hype — vegan nail care products</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-vegan-nail-care-products/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 03:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-vegan-nail-care-products/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="discover-tiktoks-favorite-vegan-nail-care"&gt;Discover TikTok&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Vegan Nail Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Irene first stumbled upon Cyklar&amp;rsquo;s vegan nail care line on TikTok, she was skeptical. Could a brand that gained fame through social media truly deliver on its promises? It seemed every influencer was raving about its environmentally conscious ingredients and transformative results. But Irene, a devoted fan of all things natural, decided to try it for herself. “I’ve always been about clean beauty,” she shared. “But finding a vegan product that works and doesn’t compromise quality? That’s rare.” With the first application, Irene noticed a difference. Her nails felt stronger, healthier. The subtle scent of essential oils lingered, a gentle reminder of nature&amp;rsquo;s power. It was a small change, but it felt significant — a step towards a more sustainable beauty routine.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>