<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Vegan-Antifungal-Nail-Care on Nailak Blog</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/tags/vegan-antifungal-nail-care/</link><description>Recent content in Vegan-Antifungal-Nail-Care on Nailak Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 13:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.nailak.com/tags/vegan-antifungal-nail-care/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Refy Lip Stick — Nail fungus and brittle nails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/26/refy-lip-stick-nail-fungus-and-brittle-nails/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 13:19:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/26/refy-lip-stick-nail-fungus-and-brittle-nails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="refy-lip-stick-mood-fix-nail-fungus-and-brittleness"&gt;Refy Lip Stick Mood, Fix Nail Fungus and Brittleness&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The mug was warm. Her lipstick, a fresh swipe of Refy Lip Stick in a shade that made her look instantly awake, caught the light. It was one of those tiny wins that set the tone for the day. Then she noticed it. A peeling edge on her thumbnail. A pale line on her index finger. A small crumble at the tip that snagged her sweater. You can smooth it once. Twice. But brittle nails have a way of asking for attention.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>These Travel Day Outfits are SO Cozy, You’ll Never Want to Take Them Off! — Nail fungus prevention tips</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/25/these-travel-day-outfits-are-so-cozy-youll-never-want-to-take-them-off-nail-fungus-prevention-tips/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 16:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/25/these-travel-day-outfits-are-so-cozy-youll-never-want-to-take-them-off-nail-fungus-prevention-tips/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="cozy-travel-outfits--nail-fungus-prevention-tips"&gt;Cozy Travel Outfits + Nail Fungus Prevention Tips&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. A day later, at 4:45 a.m., she was zipping a carry-on, slipping into a matching knit set, and double-knotting her sneakers. Travel day. The airport hummed like a beehive. Everything felt a touch too bright, too loud, too fast.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>