<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Nail-Care on Nailak Blog</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/tags/nail-care/</link><description>Recent content in Nail-Care on Nailak Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:05:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.nailak.com/tags/nail-care/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Liquid Blush vs Powder Blush: Which Formula Delivers the Best Results for Your Skin? — Vegan nail oil for cuticles</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/liquid-blush-vs-powder-blush-which-formula-delivers-the-best-results-for-your-skin-vegan-nail-oil-for-cuticles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:05:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/liquid-blush-vs-powder-blush-which-formula-delivers-the-best-results-for-your-skin-vegan-nail-oil-for-cuticles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="liquid-or-powder-blush-plus-vegan-cuticle-care"&gt;Liquid or Powder Blush? Plus Vegan Cuticle Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The steam curled around her cup, blending with the delicate scent of citrus from last night’s cuticle oil. On her cheeks, the flush was just right: not too glowy, not too matte. She’d finally nailed it — the balance between liquid blush and powder blush — and found a rhythm that made busy mornings feel less like a rush and more like a ritual.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Makeup and Beauty Blog Monday Poll, Vol. 897 — Essential oils for cuticle health</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-and-beauty-blog-monday-poll-vol.-897-essential-oils-for-cuticle-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:50:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-and-beauty-blog-monday-poll-vol.-897-essential-oils-for-cuticle-health/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="essential-oils-for-cuticle-health-a-modern-guide"&gt;Essential Oils for Cuticle Health: A Modern Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. Maybe you’ve had a moment like that too. A pause. Steam rising from your mug. The weight of your day arranging itself around a single choice: be gentle with yourself, or keep rushing. It’s often our hands that tell the truth first. They show our pace. They show our habits. And when the skin around our nails turns tight, rough, or ragged, that little flare of discomfort can echo through everything we do.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How to Do Spooky (But Cute!) Halloween Nails at Home — How to fix nail peeling and splitting</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/how-to-do-spooky-but-cute-halloween-nails-at-home-how-to-fix-nail-peeling-and-splitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/how-to-do-spooky-but-cute-halloween-nails-at-home-how-to-fix-nail-peeling-and-splitting/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="spooky-cute-halloween-nails-at-home-no-damage"&gt;Spooky-Cute Halloween Nails at Home (No Damage)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break—the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. The brisk October air pressed against the window. A sweater cuff grazed knuckles that had known too many rushed dishwashing sessions and not enough cuticle oil. There were tiny splits at the free edge, a nick from an old metal file, and the faint ghost of last week’s polish.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The 10 Most Common Addictions: A Guide To Breaking Free — Hangnail prevention tips</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/the-10-most-common-addictions-a-guide-to-breaking-free-hangnail-prevention-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/the-10-most-common-addictions-a-guide-to-breaking-free-hangnail-prevention-tips/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hangnail-prevention-break-the-picking-habit"&gt;Hangnail Prevention: Break the Picking Habit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She noticed it during her quick coffee stop—the tiniest flap of skin by her thumbnail, catching softly on the paper cup. It was nothing dramatic, just a whisper of roughness against a smooth morning. On the walk back, the urge bloomed. She told herself she would leave it alone, but the familiar loop began anyway—rub, tug, relief, sting. The skin reddened. Hand sanitizer made it burn. Later, typing hurt. She tucked the finger into a sleeve like a secret.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>La Mer vs Carrot &amp; Stick — Natural vs synthetic nail care products</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/la-mer-vs-carrot-stick-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/la-mer-vs-carrot-stick-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care-products/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="la-mer-vs-carrot--stick-natural-vs-synthetic-nail-care"&gt;La Mer vs Carrot &amp;amp; Stick: Natural vs Synthetic Nail Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She glanced at her hands during a morning coffee break — the soft sheen of care was the quiet reminder that small rituals matter. A few hours earlier, she’d patted in a velvety cream between emails, massaged a drop of oil into her cuticles, and slipped on dish gloves before tackling the sink. Nothing glamorous. Just calm, consistent care. Now, the cuticles looked neat, the nail beds hydrated, and even the faint ridges felt softer under her thumb. It wasn’t about a perfect manicure; it was about feeling composed in the small ways that carry you through a day.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>