<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>How to Strengthen Brittle Nails on Nailak Blog – Nail Care, Cuticle Oil &amp; Beauty Tips</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/tags/how-to-strengthen-brittle-nails/</link><description>Recent content in How to Strengthen Brittle Nails on Nailak Blog – Nail Care, Cuticle Oil &amp; Beauty Tips</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:36:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.nailak.com/tags/how-to-strengthen-brittle-nails/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exercises That Help Combat Muscle Loss on GLP-1s — Non toxic nail polish alternatives</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/exercises-that-help-combat-muscle-loss-on-glp-1s-non-toxic-nail-polish-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/exercises-that-help-combat-muscle-loss-on-glp-1s-non-toxic-nail-polish-alternatives/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="exercises-for-glp-1-muscle-loss--non-toxic-nail-polish"&gt;Exercises for GLP-1 Muscle Loss + Non-Toxic Nail Polish&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She paused at the kitchen counter, steam curling from her mug, and noticed her hands. A soft, healthy sheen on her nails. A strength she hadn’t seen in a while returning to her forearms. It wasn’t dramatic. It wasn’t loud. But it felt like her body whispering, I’m rebuilding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, clothes had started to fit differently. The number on the scale shifted, and with it came a wave of mixed emotions. She’d started a GLP-1 medication after a long talk with her doctor, hoping to steady habits that always felt just out of reach. Appetite eased. Meals simplified. Yet, there was a new question: was she losing more than she intended?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Avora Immersive Experience — How to moisturize nails and cuticles</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/avora-immersive-experience-how-to-moisturize-nails-and-cuticles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/avora-immersive-experience-how-to-moisturize-nails-and-cuticles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="avora-london-guide--how-to-moisturize-nails--cuticles"&gt;Avora London Guide + How to Moisturize Nails &amp;amp; Cuticles&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The doors swing open and the room glows green, like a rainforest after rain. A soft mist curls through the light. The bartender—part scientist, part storyteller—slides a beaker across the bar and it hums with neon. A flower-shaped garnish opens under the rim. You sip and the flavor shifts: bright citrus, then cool pine, a whisper of floral that you can’t quite name. A hush ripples through the crowd as a curtain lifts and reveals a corridor of glowing vines. You step into the next chamber and the floor responds to your footsteps, a galaxy blooming with every move.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>MAKEUP PALETTES That Do It All — Nail strengthening treatments</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-palettes-that-do-it-all-nail-strengthening-treatments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/makeup-palettes-that-do-it-all-nail-strengthening-treatments/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="makeup-palettes-that-do-it-all--nail-strengtheners"&gt;Makeup Palettes That Do It All + Nail Strengtheners&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lights in the airport restroom hummed like a nervous bee. I had eight minutes before boarding and the kind of face that looked like it had slept under an armrest — because it had. A half-empty coffee rattled in the trash. Somewhere beyond security, a child giggled at the way the automatic sinks came to life. I unzipped a small pouch, the only one I’d brought for “getting ready,” and laid its contents on the cool counter.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>What Are Exosomes, The Lastest Skincare Ingredient Exciting Dermatologists? — What causes brittle nails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/what-are-exosomes-the-lastest-skincare-ingredient-exciting-dermatologists-what-causes-brittle-nails/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/what-are-exosomes-the-lastest-skincare-ingredient-exciting-dermatologists-what-causes-brittle-nails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="exosomes-in-skincare-and-brittle-nails-explained"&gt;Exosomes in Skincare and Brittle Nails Explained&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plane’s air vents hissed like a desert wind. By hour six, the skin on my hands felt papery, and the ridges on my thumbnails caught on the lining of my jacket. In the hotel bathroom, the mirror wobbled with a hum as the extractor fan worked. Harsh light exposed what travel always tries to hide: dullness around the eyes, a chalky veil on cheeks, and that unmistakable snag when a brittle nail meets a zipper.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>12 Hidden Rosacea Triggers You Need to Know, According to Dermatologists — DIY nail oil blend</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-you-need-to-know-according-to-dermatologists-diy-nail-oil-blend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-you-need-to-know-according-to-dermatologists-diy-nail-oil-blend/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-dermatologists-warn-about"&gt;12 Hidden Rosacea Triggers Dermatologists Warn About&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first time it happened, it felt like a match drawn across my cheekbones. Late afternoon sun bathed the café in Porto, the table crowded with friends and small plates—salty cheeses, olives slick with oil, a smear of piri-piri heat. Someone topped off my glass. The moment the wine hit, warmth bloomed across my face. Eyes prickled. Skin tightened. I reached for a napkin and realized my fingertips smelled faintly of citrus from the cuticle oil I’d rolled on an hour earlier.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>This TikTok Viral Bodycare Brand Lives Up to the Hype — How to use cuticle oil properly</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-how-to-use-cuticle-oil-properly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 23:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-how-to-use-cuticle-oil-properly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="how-to-use-cuticle-oil-the-right-way-anywhere"&gt;How to Use Cuticle Oil the Right Way, Anywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a certain sound the airport makes when a storm stalls departures. Coffee machines tempo into a low hiss. A thousand rolling suitcases drum the tiles. A PA crackles, apologizes, then goes silent. You rub your hands together because the terminal AC runs too cold, because winter air steals moisture, because the sanitizer pump by the gate is impossible to pass without a press. Your fingers feel tight and a little sore. A rough edge snags your sweater. You wince.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>This TikTok Viral Bodycare Brand Lives Up to the Hype — vegan nail care products</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-vegan-nail-care-products/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 03:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-vegan-nail-care-products/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="discover-tiktoks-favorite-vegan-nail-care"&gt;Discover TikTok&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Vegan Nail Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Irene first stumbled upon Cyklar&amp;rsquo;s vegan nail care line on TikTok, she was skeptical. Could a brand that gained fame through social media truly deliver on its promises? It seemed every influencer was raving about its environmentally conscious ingredients and transformative results. But Irene, a devoted fan of all things natural, decided to try it for herself. “I’ve always been about clean beauty,” she shared. “But finding a vegan product that works and doesn’t compromise quality? That’s rare.” With the first application, Irene noticed a difference. Her nails felt stronger, healthier. The subtle scent of essential oils lingered, a gentle reminder of nature&amp;rsquo;s power. It was a small change, but it felt significant — a step towards a more sustainable beauty routine.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>