<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>News on Nailak Blog</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/categories/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on Nailak Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:05:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.nailak.com/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>12 Hidden Rosacea Triggers You Need to Know, According to Dermatologists — DIY nail oil blend</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-you-need-to-know-according-to-dermatologists-diy-nail-oil-blend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/20/12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-you-need-to-know-according-to-dermatologists-diy-nail-oil-blend/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="12-hidden-rosacea-triggers-dermatologists-warn-about"&gt;12 Hidden Rosacea Triggers Dermatologists Warn About&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first time it happened, it felt like a match drawn across my cheekbones. Late afternoon sun bathed the café in Porto, the table crowded with friends and small plates—salty cheeses, olives slick with oil, a smear of piri-piri heat. Someone topped off my glass. The moment the wine hit, warmth bloomed across my face. Eyes prickled. Skin tightened. I reached for a napkin and realized my fingertips smelled faintly of citrus from the cuticle oil I’d rolled on an hour earlier.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>This TikTok Viral Bodycare Brand Lives Up to the Hype — How to use cuticle oil properly</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-how-to-use-cuticle-oil-properly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 23:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-how-to-use-cuticle-oil-properly/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="how-to-use-cuticle-oil-the-right-way-anywhere"&gt;How to Use Cuticle Oil the Right Way, Anywhere&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a certain sound the airport makes when a storm stalls departures. Coffee machines tempo into a low hiss. A thousand rolling suitcases drum the tiles. A PA crackles, apologizes, then goes silent. You rub your hands together because the terminal AC runs too cold, because winter air steals moisture, because the sanitizer pump by the gate is impossible to pass without a press. Your fingers feel tight and a little sore. A rough edge snags your sweater. You wince.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kylie Jenner Reheated The 'King Kylie' Aesthetic With Her 10-Year Anniversary Collection — Best cuticle oil brands</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/kylie-jenner-reheated-the-king-kylie-aesthetic-with-her-10-year-anniversary-collection-best-cuticle-oil-brands/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/kylie-jenner-reheated-the-king-kylie-aesthetic-with-her-10-year-anniversary-collection-best-cuticle-oil-brands/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="best-cuticle-oils-for-reviving-your-nails"&gt;Best Cuticle Oils for Reviving Your Nails&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the bustling world of beauty, trends come and go with the swiftness of a New York minute. It&amp;rsquo;s 2016 again, and the nostalgia of the &amp;ldquo;King Kylie&amp;rdquo; era has swept us back into the vibrant world of bold lip kits and shimmering highlighters. But as any beauty enthusiast knows, the foundation of any great look isn&amp;rsquo;t just the makeup—it&amp;rsquo;s the care that goes into the canvas itself. This time, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about something that often gets overlooked in the beauty routine: your nails.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ICYMI: Maria Grazia Chiuri Returns to Fendi, Boy Smells Opens First Flagship Pop-Up &amp; What Brands Get Out of Beauty New York — How to grow nails faster naturally</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/icymi-maria-grazia-chiuri-returns-to-fendi-boy-smells-opens-first-flagship-pop-up-what-brands-get-out-of-beauty-new-york-how-to-grow-nails-faster-naturally/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/icymi-maria-grazia-chiuri-returns-to-fendi-boy-smells-opens-first-flagship-pop-up-what-brands-get-out-of-beauty-new-york-how-to-grow-nails-faster-naturally/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="grow-nails-faster-naturally-expert-tips"&gt;Grow Nails Faster Naturally: Expert Tips&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picture this: You’re scrolling through your favorite fashion blog, and you stumble upon an article about the latest trends in nail art. The vibrant colors and intricate designs are captivating, and you can almost feel the urge to book your next manicure appointment. But there’s a hitch — your nails seem to grow at a snail’s pace. You’ve tried everything from nail strengtheners to biotin supplements, yet nothing seems to make a real difference. You sigh, feeling the frustration that many share when it comes to achieving those perfectly long and healthy nails that are always Instagram-ready.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Glossy Pop Newsletter: Lancôme is making moves to become every bride’s go-to glam — Nail growth tips at home</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/glossy-pop-newsletter-lanc%C3%B4me-is-making-moves-to-become-every-brides-go-to-glam-nail-growth-tips-at-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/glossy-pop-newsletter-lanc%C3%B4me-is-making-moves-to-become-every-brides-go-to-glam-nail-growth-tips-at-home/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="lancômes-bridal-glamour--nail-growth-tips"&gt;Lancôme&amp;rsquo;s Bridal Glamour &amp;amp; Nail Growth Tips&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine walking down the aisle, the soft hum of music enveloping you, and every eye in the room is on you. Your gown flows like a gentle stream, and your makeup — impeccable, timeless, and effortlessly radiant. For many brides, this dream moment is incomplete without the perfect makeup brand. Lancôme is stepping up to be that brand. It&amp;rsquo;s not just about the makeup; it&amp;rsquo;s about embodying elegance and sophistication on one of the most memorable days of your life.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Ulta Beauty’s Marketplace Launch Sparks Customer Backlash — Nail oil vs cuticle cream</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/ulta-beautys-marketplace-launch-sparks-customer-backlash-nail-oil-vs-cuticle-cream/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/ulta-beautys-marketplace-launch-sparks-customer-backlash-nail-oil-vs-cuticle-cream/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="ulta-beautys-new-marketplace-what-you-need-to-know"&gt;Ulta Beauty&amp;rsquo;s New Marketplace: What You Need to Know&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine walking into a store, your senses enveloped by the aroma of countless beauty products, each promising to transform your routine. You’re not just shopping; you&amp;rsquo;re embarking on a self-care journey. Ulta Beauty has long been a destination for beauty enthusiasts seeking everything from cult-favorite mascaras to the latest skincare innovations. In its latest move, Ulta unveiled the UB Marketplace, a digital expansion designed to offer even more variety. However, this launch hasn&amp;rsquo;t been without its hiccups.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Best Celebrity Bobs to Wear in Any Season — How to prevent hangnails</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/the-best-celebrity-bobs-to-wear-in-any-season-how-to-prevent-hangnails/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/the-best-celebrity-bobs-to-wear-in-any-season-how-to-prevent-hangnails/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="celebrity-bobs--hangnail-solutions"&gt;Celebrity Bobs &amp;amp; Hangnail Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the likes of Taylor Swift and Zendaya strutted onto the red carpet with their chic bob hairstyles, fans around the globe were mesmerized. The bob, with its timeless elegance and effortless charm, has taken over Hollywood. It’s not just a hairstyle—it&amp;rsquo;s a statement. But beneath the glamorous exterior lies a common beauty woe that even celebrities can’t escape: hangnails. These tiny, pesky skin tears are more than just a minor annoyance; they can be painful and even lead to infections. Imagine this: you’re about to shake hands with someone important, and there it is—a snag. It’s a moment many have experienced, yet few talk about openly.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>We're Moving! — non-toxic nail care</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/were-moving-non-toxic-nail-care/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 04:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/were-moving-non-toxic-nail-care/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="non-toxic-nail-care-the-future-of-beauty"&gt;Non-Toxic Nail Care: The Future of Beauty&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When UberChic Beauty announced its warehouse move, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a change of address. For many loyal customers, it marked the end of an era—eight years of vibrant nail art and innovative non-toxic products. The move was a testament to the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth and evolution, a reflection of how far the industry has come. “Thank you for your amazing support and for the BEST eight years we could have ever asked for,” read the heartfelt note from the founder. As fans rushed to place orders before the temporary shipping pause, the excitement was palpable. The new year promised fresh beginnings and new developments, including a special mini plate called &amp;ldquo;Happy Birthday&amp;rdquo; to celebrate the milestone.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>This TikTok Viral Bodycare Brand Lives Up to the Hype — vegan nail care products</title><link>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-vegan-nail-care-products/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 03:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.nailak.com/posts/2025/10/19/this-tiktok-viral-bodycare-brand-lives-up-to-the-hype-vegan-nail-care-products/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="discover-tiktoks-favorite-vegan-nail-care"&gt;Discover TikTok&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Vegan Nail Care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Irene first stumbled upon Cyklar&amp;rsquo;s vegan nail care line on TikTok, she was skeptical. Could a brand that gained fame through social media truly deliver on its promises? It seemed every influencer was raving about its environmentally conscious ingredients and transformative results. But Irene, a devoted fan of all things natural, decided to try it for herself. “I’ve always been about clean beauty,” she shared. “But finding a vegan product that works and doesn’t compromise quality? That’s rare.” With the first application, Irene noticed a difference. Her nails felt stronger, healthier. The subtle scent of essential oils lingered, a gentle reminder of nature&amp;rsquo;s power. It was a small change, but it felt significant — a step towards a more sustainable beauty routine.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>